Deni Mintsaev

Web developer

Contacts

cube327@tuta.io denimintsaev.com github.com/dmint789 linkedin.com/in/deni-mintsaev

Skills

HTML

CSS

SCSS • Less • Tailwind

Javascript • Typescript

Vue • Vuex • Nuxt

React • Redux • Next

React Native

Express

MySQL

MongoDB

Docker

Nginx

Git • Github

Linux

Languages

Russian - native

English - IELTS 8.0

Japanese - N2

German - B1

Education

BA (Hons) Japanese Studies

University of Manchester

September 2018 - June 2022

Manchester, UK

Work Experience

Web-Most | eljur.ru

Front-end developer (full-time)

October 2022 - November 2022

- Creating system for taking psychological tests, viewing the results, monitoring the current status of each student and managing the whole system.
- Rebuilding old pages using Vue + Vuex + Less and adding new features for a website used for school attendance, grades, etc.

World Cube Association | worldcubeassociation.org

Full-stack developer

June 2021 - present

• Adding new features and modernizing old code using RoR + React + MySQL, while working with a global team of developers.

Personal Projects

Kanji Sorter Web App

denimintsaev.com/kanjisorter

Sorts and filters Chinese or Japanese characters from an input in various ways. Allows saving personal kanji list in the cloud. Aids in the process of learning the Chinese and Japanese writing systems.

Statistics Tracker Phone App

github.com/dmint789/stat-tracker

Mobile app made in React Native with Typescript used for tracking and sorting various daily statistics, like things related to hobbies, work, health, etc.

About Me

After over 10 years of programming, I have gained experience in many different IT fields ranging from system administration to mobile app development and even game development. My specialty is web development, where I have experience in creating full-stack websites and deploying them to Linux servers. It also helps that I use Linux myself and know a great deal about how to utilize the OS effectively. I also have experience with working in a team of developers, good leadership and communication skills, and the ability to learn new technologies at a rapid pace. I aim to work in a company with great potential, while continuing to improve my skills in web development and IT in general.